iponsel.com 2009-12-01

# Windows Mobile Themes - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Statement**  
The follows is the Privacy Statement for Iponsel.com network websites.  
Please read this statement regarding our blogs. If you have questions please ask us via contact [at] iponsel.com ( Please replace [at] with @). 

**Ownership of Information**  
Iponsel.com is the sole owner of any information collected on our websites.

**Use of Cookies**  
Currently we assign cookies to our readers in order to save their preferences. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

**Third Party Cookies**  
We use other third-parties advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.

 **Update 2-April-2009**  
To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies like Google that use the DART cookie enables, that place ads on our web site. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies, with the help of cookies, may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policy of each those websites. Privacy Policy of Google and how to opt out of the user of DART cookie is available at [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
